do.  Now let us understand
what are the important triggers for today.  Janvi is with us to give you the complete details on
which news will be in the headlines and also
on Q3 business updates and results.
Good
morning Janvi.  First, explain the key triggers
and consequences that are likely to occur and have occurred.
Absolutely good morning.  If we talk about today's results, the
insurance space will be in focus
because the results of ICICI Almbard, ICICI P will
come after the market closes.
Along with this, the numbers of Tata Alexi from IT company will be
seen coming today
after the market closes.  X date is Authum
Investments' bonus ratio of 4:1.
Anchor lock-in of 4% equity of
Canara HSBC Life Insurance is about to end, so
keep an eye on it here.
Primary Market Update: India's
IPO of Cooking Coal is going to close today.
Got very strong subscriptions.  33.6%
six times 33.6 times if we look at it today,
this entire IPO has been subscribed.
If we look at the retail subscription, it
appears to be coming close to 10 times.  So the
focus here is on a new IPO which is going to open in the market from today,
Amagi Media Labs, its
IPO will remain open till 16th January.  The
price band has been fixed from Rs 343 to Rs 361.  The
lot size is 41 shares, which is a total
issue size of approximately Rs 1790 crore.
If we look at the fresh issue component, it is worth Rs 816
crore.  The company has raised Rs 84 crore from anchor investors
and huge amounts are
visible in the anchor book.
Talking about the results, HCL Tech
's results came yesterday after the market closed.
Overall, the company's revenue
growth drove the performances.
Very good results were obtained here.  The company's
revenue has increased by about 6%.
If we look at the operating profit, it
seems to be increasing to Rs 6280 crore.
Margin company has expanded here.
If we look at the margins of 17.2%, they
seem to be coming down to 18.6%.  The company's
advanced AI revenue growth is expected to be
around 20% in consensus currency terms.   The
company has also revised its FI 26 guidance.
If we talk about the results of TCS, then there are very good
results here.  The company's outlook
looks even better than the results.  The company's revenue has
increased by about 2%.  Operating profits are
also up 2%.  The margins of the company are
stable.  But the future outlook of the company is
looking quite good
in the results and if we talk about the cash results, the
numbers of Anand Rathi Wealth have come and the
numbers are looking good.  Revenue has
increased by 22%.  If we look at the AUM of the company, there is an
increase of about 30% here.
If we look at the profits, they have increased by 30%.
If we look at the total net inflow, there
is a decline of up to 6%.
Absolutely.  Now Jami will understand from you which
news and which shares are going to be in the headlines today.
Absolutely, if we talk about today's focus shares, then the
OFS of Andhra Cement
for retail investors was closed yesterday.  So if we
look at its subscription, 52% of it is
retail subscription.
Kalpatra Limited has released its Q3 update.
Presales in Q3
declined by 14%.  It is seen decreasing from Rs 108 crore to Rs 870 crore.  If we
look at the sections also, there is an
increase of 17%.  It seems to be increasing to around Rs 1100 crore
here.
Focus will have to be kept on companies like GMDC Hindstan Copper because
if we look at rare earth magnets, a big meeting was held.   The
government held a
critical meeting with more than 20
stakeholders regarding rare earth magnets.
This discussion was seen taking place regarding the scheme worth Rs 7280 crore.
Biocon's QIP opened yesterday.
If we look at the floor price, it has been fixed at ₹387,
which is
at a premium of about 4.5% over the current price.  The
board had already decided to raise Rs 4150 crore through QIP.
KPI Green
Energy KP Group is seen signing a deal worth Rs 4000 crore with the Gujarat government
for renewable projects.
If we look at Crystal Integrated Services in the end, the
company worth about Rs 275 crore is
seen getting the order.